Kui Wang

1122 W. Center St., Rochester, MN 57902 | +1(541)602-8182 | wangkuigis@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/kui-wang

Profile

I am a highly accomplished, skilled and knowledgeable computer science engineer with strong expertise in JavaScript and visualization by D3.js. I am interested in positions with great opportunities to provide data visualization solutions for medical informatics research.

Education

Master of Engineering, Computer Science

Sept. 2015 - Jun. 2016

Oregon State University, Corvallis, OR, USA

• Courses: Algorithms & Data Structures, Database Management System, Computer Architecture, Parallel Programming, Operating Systems, Computer Graphics, Computer Vision.

Bachelor of Science, Geographic Information System

Sept. 2009 – Jun. 2013

China Agricultural University, Beijing, China

• Courses: Digital Image Processing for Remote Sensing, Principles of Digital Surveying and Mapping, Spatial Analysis, Photogrammetry, Principle of Remote Sensing, GPS Principle.

Experience

Research Trainee Dec. 2016 – Present

Mayo Clinic, Department of Health Sciences Research, Rochester, MN

- Design and implement interactive online visualization tools for high-dimensional data in healthcare.
- Develop rich interactive visualizations of structured data and geographical information.
- The personal website is updated in https://wangku.github.io/Visualizations/KuiWang.html.

Remote Sensing Internship

May. 2013 – Jun. 2013

Ministry of Land and Resources, Land Management Center, Beijing, China

- Collect remote sensing data from the entire country and conduct accuracy analysis.
- Process remote sensing data with ArcGIS and field studies to determine land use types.

Projects

Solar System Engine

Sept. 2015

- Realize a 3D animated solar system simulation by using OpenCL and OpenGL.
- Design a particle system with concept of parallel programming to present the comet tail in an ellipse orbit.

Automated System Testing

Jun. 2016

• Implement the fuzz testing modules running in qeum Linux system kernel to automatically detect coding errors and security loopholes.

Publications

Shen, S., Wang, K., Shen, Z., & Zhao, M. (2013). *Design and implementation of invasive alien plants online survey system based on Google Maps.* Journal of Central South University (Science and Technology), S1.